A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.27 (A2001) FA488
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2001.034: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1978-2001; AC.2001.034; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - Health Sciences (HS), AC.2001.034.3; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - HS 9502 - CENTRO DE INVESTIGACIONES ECOLOGICAS DEL SURESTE (MEXICO) - HEALTH TRACT WITHIN ITS MASTER OF SCIENCE PROGRAM, 1993-1996 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9509 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - "MOLECULAR EPIDEMIOLOGY OF PNEUMOCOCCI" PROJECT, 1994-2000 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9520 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - MEETINGS OF INTERNATIONAL FORUM FOR SOCIAL SCIENCES AND HEALTH, 1994-1997 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9522 - KAROLINSKA INSTITUTE (SWEDEN) - DOCUMENT SWEDISH EXPERIENCE FOR POLICYMAKERS IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1995-2001 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9523 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - INSTITUTE OF MEDICINE - GLOBAL HEALTH RISKS EFFECT ON U.S. HEALTH AND ECONOMY, 1995-1997 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9526 - TULANE UNIVERSITY - GATHER BIBLIOGRAPHIC MATERIAL FOR DOCTURAL STUDENT IN ZAIRE, 1995-1997 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9528 - MEXICAN HEALTH FOUNDATION - INTERNATIONAL CLEARINGHOUSE OF HEALTH SYSTEM REFORM INITIATIVES, 1994-1997 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9601 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - CHANGING ROLE OF UNITED NATIONS IN INTERNATIONAL HEALTH, 1995-1997 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9602 - PAN AMERICAN HEALTH ORGANIZATION - HEALTH PROMOTION AND VIOLENCE PREVENTION PROJECT, 1995-1997 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9605 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - SERIES OF CONFERENCES AND PROGRAMMATICALLY FEASIBLE INVESTMENT STRATEGIES IN HEALTH FOR THE FUTURE, 1996-1997 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9607 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - SYMPOSIUM, "GATEWAY TO WORLD HEALTH: NEW SCIENCE AND STRATEGIES IN PUBLIC HEALTH", 1996-1998 (Box R3407)
    - HS 9608 - AUSTRALIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY- HEALTH TRANSITION SECRETARIAT, 1988-1999 (Box R3408)
    - HS 9608 - AUSTRALIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY- HEALTH TRANSITION SECRETARIAT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1988-1999 (Box R3408)
    - HS 9610 - POPULATION COUNCIL - IMPROVEMENT OF WOMEN'S REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH IN EGYPT, 1996-1998 (Box R3408)
    - HS 9701 - HYDE, KARIN A. L. - REPORT ON SEXUAL EDUCATION PROGRAMS IN AFRICAN SCHOOLS, 1996-1997 (Box R3408)
    - HS 9613 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY- ANTI-SMOKING PROJECT IN CHINA, 1990-1998 (Box R3408)
    - HS 9614 - HEALTH SYSTEMS TRUST (SOUTH AFRICA) - HEALTH SYSTEMS AND PLANNING SKILLS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1996-1998 (Box R3408)
    - HS 9615 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - GLOBAL HEALTH RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT FORUM, 1996-1998 (Box R3408)
    - HS 9703 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - "INTERNATIONAL HEALTH AND DEVELOPMENT IN THE 21ST CENTURY", 1997-1998 (Box R3408)
    - HS 9704 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - MEETINGS ON THE ROLE, CAPACITY AND PERFORMANCE OF INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATIONS FOR ADVANCING WORLD HEALTH, 1996-1997 (Box R3409)
  - Population Sciences (PS), AC.2001.034.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - PS 9409 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - RESEARCH AND TRAINING IN REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY AND ENDOCRINOLOGY, 1978-1998 (Box R3409)
    - PS 9433 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY - POPULATION, 1987-1998 (Box R3409)
- AC.2001.038: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1983-2000; AC.2001.038; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
  - Population Sciences (PS), AC.2001.038.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - PS 9438 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF MEDICAL SCIENCES- SPERM MEMBRANE PROTEINS, 1983-1998 (Box R3410)
    - PS 9501 - UNIVERSITY OF BAHIA - REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY, 1979-1997 (Box R3410)
    - PS 9503 - ASOCIACION DOMINICANA PRO-BIENESTAR DE LA FAMILIA, INC.- STRENGTHEN DEPT. OF BIOMEDICAL RESEARCH, 1992-1998 (Box R3411)
    - PS 9514 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH - USING SCOUTS TO EXTEND FAMILY EDUCATION, 1994-1998 (Box R3411)
    - PS 9517 - COMMONWEALTH MEDICAL ASSOCIATION (ENGLAND) - ADOLESCENT REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH ISSUES, 1995-1998 (Box R3411)
    - PS 9518 - CHINA POPULATION INFORMATION AND RESEARCH CENTER- IMPACT OF FAMILY PLANNING ON CHINESE WOMEN'S LIVES, 1995-1998 (Box R3411)
    - PS 9526 - POPULATION ACTION INTERNATIONAL - ICPO-RELATED U.S. PUBLIC INFORMATION AND EDUCATION CAMPAIGN, 1995-1997 (Box R3411)
    - PS 9527 - INTERNATIONAL WOMEN'S HEALTH COALITION- PUBLIC EDUCATION PROGRAM IN THE UNITED STATES, 1995-1997 (Box R3411)
    - PS 9605 - SINGH, JYOTI SHANKAR- MONOGRAPH ON ICPD, 1996-1998 (Box R3411)
    - PS 9607 - McMASTER UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - ADOLESCENT SEXUAL AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH INTERVENTIONS, 1996-1998 (Box R3411)
    - PS 9615 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN - CONSEQUENCES OF ADOLESCENT CHILDBEARING IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1996-1998 (Box R3411)
    - PS 9619 - POPULATION ASSOCIATION OF AMERICA -1997 ANNUAL MEETINGS, 1996-1998 (Box R3411)
    - PS 9703 - SOCIAL SCIENCE AND MEDICINE AFRICA NETWORK (KENYA) - THIRD SOCIAL SCIENCES AND HEALTH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE, 1996-1998 (Box R3411)
  - BD, AC.2001.038.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - BD 9611 - MEDIATORS FOUNDATION - CAMPAIGN FOR COMMON GROUND, 1995-1998 (Box R3411)
    - BD 9614 - SAN FRANCISCO STATE UNIVERSITY - CENTER FOR INTEGRATION AND IMPROVEMENT OF JOURNALISM - NEWS WATCH PROJECT, 1996-1998 (Box R3412)
    - BD 9622 - YOUTH LAW CENTER - RIGHTS OF MINORITY YOUTH IN JUVENILE JUSTICE SYSTEM, 1995-1999 (Box R3412)
    - BD 9701 - CARTER CENTER - CONFERENCE ON COMMUNITY BUILDING AND CITIES, 1996-2000 (Box R3412)
    - BD 9713 - FOUNDATION FOR THE NATIONAL CAPITAL REGION - D.C. AGENDA, 1996-1998 (Box R3412)
    - BD 9713 - FOUNDATION FOR THE NATIONAL CAPITAL REGION - D.C. AGENDA - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-1998 (Box R3412)
    - BD 9714 - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND (COLLEGE PARK) - GOVERNMENT AND POLITICS PROFESSORSHIP ENDOWMENT, 1997-1998 (Box R3412)
  - International Philanthropy (IP), AC.2001.038.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 94-8200-1 PUERTO RICO COMMUNITY FOUNDATION - INSTITUTE FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF PHILANTHROPY, 1993-1997 (Box R3412)
- AC.2001.045: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1986-2000; AC.2001.045; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - International Security (IS), AC.2001.045.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - IS 9330 - CENTRE FOR POLICY RESEARCH (INDIA) - SECURITY CONCERNS, 1992-1998 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9409 - 94-8210-9 - EMORY UNIVERSITY - NUCLEAR PROLIFERATION TENSIONS IN THE KOREAN PENNINSULA, 1993-1999 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9425 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - INTERNATIONAL SECURITY - NON-PROLIFERATION PEOPLE'S REPUBLIC OF CHINA, 1994-1997 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9602 - SETON HALL UNIVERSITY - "SETON HALL PROJECT ON KOREA", 1994-1999 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9607 - (INTERNATIONAL SECURITY)- PROGRAM OPERATIONS, 1994-1999 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9611 - SETON HALL UNIVERSITY - MISSION TO NORTH KOREA, 1995-1998 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9615 - CARNEGIE MELLON UNIVERSITY - TECHNOLOGY ISSUES IN INDIA, 1994-1997 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9619 - COUNCIL ON FOREIGN RELATIONS, INC. - NUCLEAR POLICY REVIEW PROJECT, 1996-1997 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9624 - ATLANTIC COUNCIL OF THE UNITED STATES - FURTHER REINS ON NUCLEAR WEAPONS IN EAST ASIA, 1996-1999 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9625 - PARLIAMENTARIANS FOR GLOBAL ACTION - ABOLITION OF NUCLEAR WEAPONS SIGNATURE DRIVE, 1996-1997 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9626 - OXFORD RESEARCH GROUP (ENGLAND) - SEMINAR WITH CHINESE ON NUCLEAR WEAPONS DECISION-MAKING, 1996-1997 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9633 - LAWYER'S ALLIANCE FOR WORLD SECURITY - "MOVING TOWARD NUCLEAR DISARMAMENT" PROJECT, 1996-1999 (Box R3413)
    - IS 9709 - MONTEREY INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL STUDIES - CHINESE NONPROLIFERATION AND ARMS CONTROL POLICY, 1997-1998 (Box R3414)
    - IS 9710 - MONTEREY INSTITUTE FOR INTERNATIONAL STUDIES - RUSSIA AND THE NORTH KOREAN NUCLEAR PROGRAM, 1994-1999 (Box R3414)
  - Special Interests (SI), AC.2001.045.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - SI 9410 - 94-8040-10 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION FOUNDATION - ALLIANCE FOR REDESIGNING GOVERNMENT, 1993-1996 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9506 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY- MARTIN LUTHER KING, JR. PAPERS PROJECT, 1994-1998 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9513 - AVANCE FAMILY SUPPORT AND EDUCATION PROGRAM - FIVE YEAR STRATEGIC GROWTH PLAN, 1994-1996 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9513 - AVANCE FAMILY SUPPORT AND EDUCATION PROGRAM - FIVE YEAR STRATEGIC GROWTH PLAN - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1996 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9516 - WASHINGTON CENTER FOR CHINA STUDIES- CHINA-BASED INDEPENDENT ACADEMIC RESEARCH CENTER, 1995-1996 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9522 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES- HEALTH AND MENTAL HEALTH OF IMMIGRANT FAMILIES, 1995-1999 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9604 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - CHICANO STUDIES RESEARCH CENTER- SURVEY OF MEXICAN AMERICANS, 1995-1996 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9605 - EVT EDUCATIONAL PRODUCTIONS, INC.- DOCUMENTARY "THE I'LL BE FREE TO TRAVEL HOME", 1995-1997 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9610 - MANAGEMENT SCIENCES FOR HEALTH - ADAPT BANGLADESH'S LOCAL INITIATIVE PROGRAM IN BOSTON, 1996-1997 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9612 - GOOD SHEPHERD MINISTRIES, INC. - PREPARE INNER-CITY STUDENTS FOR COLLEGE ADMISSION, 1996-1998 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9613 - NEW YORK PUBLIC LIBRARY- DIGITAL IMAGING AND INTERNET ACCESS FOR COLLECTIONS ON AFRICAN DIASPORA AND AFRICA, 1996-1999 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9615 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR THE ADVANCEMENT OF PHILANTHROPY - NATIONAL FILM ARCHIVE OF PHILANTHROPY, 1995-1996 (Box R3414)
    - SI 9617 - KOAHNIC BROADCAST CORP. - NATIONAL NATIVE-AMERICAN RADIO SYSTEM, 1996-2000 (Box R3414)
      Separated Materials
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - AIROS Program Sampler, 1999 (Item 2001.045.001)
      - National Native News, 1999 (Item 2015.045.003)
      - Native Word of the Day, November 1999 (Item 2015.045.002)
    - SI 9621 - BANGLADESH RURAL ADVANCEMENT COMMITTEE - NGO LEADERSHIP AND MANAGEMENT COURSE, 1996-1998 (Box R3415)
    - SI 9702 - BROWN UNIVERSITY - THOMAS J. WATSON JR. INSTITUTE FOR INTERNATIONAL STUDIES - MISSED OPPORTUNITIES OF THE VIETNAM WAR, 1997-1998 (Box R3415)
  - Special Programs (SP), AC.2001.045.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - SP 8837 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - PUBLIC SECTOR PERFORMANCE IN LATIN AMERICA, 1988-1997 (Box R3415)
  - African Initiatives (AI), AC.2001.045.4; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - AI 9308 - ZIMBABWE MOZAMBIQUE FRIENDSHIP ASSOCIATION (ZIMOFA) - TECHNICAL TRAINING FOR MOZAMBICAN STUDENTS, 1993-1997 (Box R3415)
    - AI 9314 - UNIVERSITY OF NAMIBIA - STRENGTHENING COOPERATIVE PROGRAMS AMONG SOUTHERN AFRICAN UNIVERSITIES, 1993-1995 (Box R3415)
    - AI 9409 - SCIENCE-BASED DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS- RF NAIROBI FIELD OFFICE, 1986-1996 (Box R3415, Box R3416)
    - AI 9508 - UNITED NATIONS CHILDREN'S FUND- GENDER SENSITIVE EDUCATIONAL KITS FOR EAST AND SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1995-1996 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9606 - (AFRICAN SCIENCE-BASED DEVELOPMENT: PROFESSIONAL PREPARATION) - PROMOTIONAL MATERIALS, 1996-1997 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9608 - UNITED NATIONS EDUCATIONAL, SCIENTIFIC AND CULTURAL ORGANIZATION (FRANCE) - WORKSHOPS ON GUIDANCE AND COUNSELING FOR AFRICAN SCHOOL-AGE GIRLS, 1996-1997 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9609 - ASSOCIATION OF AFRICAN UNIVERSITIES (GHANA)- CONFERENCE ON AFRICAN UNIVERSITY IN A RAPIDLY CHANGING GLOBAL ENVIRONMENT, 1996-1997 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9610 - UNIVERSITY OF SWAZILAND - NETWORKS AMONG WOMEN SCIENTISTS IN SOUTHERN AFRICA WORKSHOP, 1996-1997 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9615 - INTERNATIONAL FEDERATION OF WOMEN LAWYERS (KENYA)- COALITION ON VIOLENCE AGAINST WOMEN, 1996-1998 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9701 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - CONFERENCE ON AFRICAN RENEWAL, 1996-1998 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9703 - INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL EDUCATION - STRENGTHEN PHILANTHROPY IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1996-1997 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9704 - NATIONAL MUSEUMS OF KENYA- INSTITUTE OF PRIMATE RESEARCH - WORKSHOP TO ESTABLISH SCIENTIFIC COLLABORATION, 1996-1997 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9706 - DATA CENTER- THIRD WORLD RESOURCES PROJECT'S GUIDE TO AFRICA, 1993-1998 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9710 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN- SEMINAR ON GLOBAL WOMEN'S LEADERSHIP (RESCINDED), 1997 (Box R3416)
    - AI 9715 - SALZBURG SEMINAR IN AMERICAN STUDIES - SEMINAR ON GLOBAL WOMEN'S LEADERSHIP, 1997-1998 (Box R3416)
  - Separated Materials, 2001:045:001-2001:045:002
- AC.2001.055: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1970-2001; AC.2001.055; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2001.055.1; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
    - RF 88046 - Harvard University - AIDS AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH NETWORK, 1987-1995 (Box R3417)
    - RF 88072 #15 - CONSTITUENCY FOR AFRICA - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1994-1999 (Box R3417)
    - RF 89034 #145 - THIAM, AMADOU KHOUDIEDJI, 1990-1998 (Box R3417)
    - RF 89064 - FAMILY PLANNING PROGRAM EVALUATION IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1984-1996 (Box R3418)
    - RF 89064 - FAMILY PLANNING PROGRAM EVALUATION IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1984-1996 (Box R3418)
    - RF 89093 A 266 - UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - WOMEN'S STATUS AND FERTILITY IN FIVE ASIAN COUNTRIES, 1987-1996 (Box R3418)
    - RF 89093 A 267 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - WOMEN'S STATUS AND FERTILITY IN FIVE ASIAN COUNTRIES, 1990-1998 (Box R3418)
    - RF 89094 - ENVIRONMENTAL RESEARCH FELLOWSHIPS IN AGRICULTURE, 1989-1994 (Box R3418)
    - RF 89094 A 6 - REDDY, M. VIKRAM - SOIL MANAGEMENT AND FAUNA IN SEMI-ARID TROPICAL AGROECOSYSTEMS IN INDIA, 1990-2001 (Box R3418)
    - RF 90099 #66 - MAGIC THEATRE - "PAINTING FOR THE MUSEUM OF THE FUTURE", 1991-1998 (Box R3419)
    - RF 91009 #4 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY - USE AND FATE OF PESTICIDES IN UGANDA, 1991-1996 (Box R3419)
    - RF 91027 - WINROCK INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT - FOREST MANAGEMENT PROBLEMS, 1988-1998 (Box R3419)
    - RF 91032 #4 - NATIONAL MUSEUMS OF KENYA - REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY AND PRIMATES, 1988-1998 (Box R3419)
    - RF 91054 #11 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - RESEARCH PATHOGENIC VARIABILITY OF FUSARIUM UDUM, 1993-1998 (Box R3419)
    - RF 91060 #4 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA- RFLP MAPPING AND GENOME ANALYSIS IN CASSAVA, 1991-1998 (Box R3419)
    - RF 91080 #159 - MEDICAL RESEARCH COUNCIL (ENGLAND)- MALARIA RESEARCH IN GAMBIA, 1991-1997 (Box R3419)
    - RF 91080 #164 - 910080-164- NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF ALLERGY AND INFECTIOUS DISEASES ? ANOPHELES GAMBIAE VECTOR POPULATIONS, 1988-1997 (Box R3419)
    - RF 91084 - (SOCIAL SCIENCE AND LEGAL RESEARCH ON POPULATION POLICY), 1970-1994 (Box R3420, Box R3421)
    - RF 91084 - (SOCIAL SCIENCE AND LEGAL RESEARCH ON POPULATION POLICY) - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1970-1994 (Box R3420)
    - EAST-WEST CENTER- WOMEN'S STATUS AND FERTILITY IN 5 ASIAN COUNTRIES, 1991-1998 (Box R3421)
    - RF 91090 - SOCIAL SCIENCE SCHOLARSHIP ON DEVELOPMENT ISSUES IN THE THIRD WORLD, 1979-1998 (Box R3422, Box R3423)
    - RF 91090 - SOCIAL SCIENCE SCHOLARSHIP ON DEVELOPMENT ISSUES IN THE THIRD WORLD - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1979-1998 (Box R3422)
  - School Reform (SR), AC.2001.055.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - SR 9305 - UNITED NEGRO COLLEGE FUND - ESTABLISH A POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE, 1991-1997 (Box R3417)
    - SR 9505 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - MARKET SERVICE FEASIBILITY STUDY, 1995-1998 (Box R3417)
    - SR 9602 - EDITORIAL PROJECTS IN EDUCATION - MULTIMEDIA TECHNOLOGY ENHANCEMENT OF EDUCATION WEEK, 1995-1997 (Box R3417)
- AC.2001.061: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1983-2001; AC.2001.061; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2001.061.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 91090 #83 - (SOCIAL SCIENCE SCHOLARSHIP ON DEVELOPMENT ISSUES IN THE THIRD WORLD) - WORKSHOP AND CONFERENCE SUPPORT, 1983-1994 (Box R3424)
    - RF 92003 #145 - BEIJING AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY- RICE BLAST DISEASE RESISTANCE, 1992-1997 (Box R3424)
    - RF 92014 #72 - NATIONAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR FAMILY PLANNING (CHINA) - STUDY VITAMIN D BINDING PROTEIN, 1990-1997 (Box R3424)
    - RF 92017 #494 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS IN LEGAL HUMANITIES, 1992-1997 (Box R3424)
    - RF 92017 #495 - HUNTER COLLEGE - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS, CENTER FOR PUERTO RICAN STUDIES, 1992-1997 (Box R3424)
    - RF 92017 #496 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS, 1992-1998 (Box R3424)
    - RF 92017 #501 - UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - HUMANITIES RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS: CENTER FOR AFROAMERICAN AND AFRICAN STUDIES, 1992-1999 (Box R3424)
    - RF 92017 #508 - CULTURAL ASSOCIATION FOR CONTEMPORARY STUDIES (BRAZIL) - HUMANITIES FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 1991-2000 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92017 #508 - CULTURAL ASSOCIATION FOR CONTEMPORARY STUDIES (BRAZIL) - HUMANITIES FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-2000 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92038 #421 - NASINYAMA, GEORGE - ADIA: STUDY NON-TYPHOIDAL SALMONELLAE AND VTEC IN UGANDA, 1993-1997 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92038 #423 - ABDELGADIR, AZIZ- ADIA: BIOLOGICAL NITROGEN FIXATION, 1992-1997 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92038 #447 - GEBRU, GETACHEW - ADIA: FEED RESOURCES AND LAND TENURE IN ETHIOPIA, 1994-1998 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92038 #468 - KISSI, EDWARD - ADIA: "POLITICS OF INTERNATIONAL FOOD RELIEF IN AFRICA", 1994-2000 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92038 #471 - ANZALA, AGGREY OMU - ADIA: AFRICAN PROTITUTES AND HIV, 1994-2000 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92038 #475 - TSIKOANE, TUMELO - ADIA: SOCIAL HISTORY OF TB IN LESOTHO, 1993-1997 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92038 #478 - MAINGI, JOHN - ADIA: LAND USE AND VEGETATION CHANGE IN EASTERN KENYA, 1994-1997 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92038 #490 - GEBREMEDHIN, BERHANU - ADIA: ECONOMICS OF SOIL CONSERVATION INVESTMENTS IN TIGRAY REGION OF ETHIOPIA, 1994-1998 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92038 #494 - HAILE MARIAM, DAMEN - ADIA: EXTENDED FAMILY SUPPORT ON DEMAND FOR MEDICAL CARE IN ETHIOPIA, 1994-1997 (Box R3425)
    - RF 92038 #498 - ODINGA, AGNES A - ADIA: WOMEN, DISEASE, MEDICINE AND CHANGE, 1994-1997 (Box R3426)
    - RF 92038 #502 - GWAKO, LABAN - ADIA: EFFECTS OF WOMEN'S LAND TENURE SECURITY ON AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTIVITY IN WESTERN KENYA, 1994-1997 (Box R3426)
    - RF 92038 #505 - SEGOSEBE, EAGILWE - ADIA: PASTORAL MANAGEMENT IN BOTSWANA, 1994-1997 (Box R3426)
    - RF 92038 #507 - OTIENO, JOSEPH - ADIA: AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT AND ENVIRONMENTAL CHANGE IN KENYA, 1995-1998 (Box R3426)
    - RF 92038 #509 - OWUSU, FRANCIS - ADIA: URBAN SURVIVIAL STRATEGIES AND ECONOMIC RESTRUCTURING IN GHANA, 1995-1997 (Box R3426)
    - RF 92054 #4 - CORPORACION PARA EL DESARROLLO DE LAS CIENCIAS VEGETALES EN AMERICA LATINA- PLANT SCIENCES IN LATIN AMERICA, 1990-1998 (Box R3426, Box R3427)
    - RF 92060 #2 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - GENE TAGGING, 1989-2001 (Box R3427)
    - RF 92087 #25 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - CHINESE FAMILY PLANNING, 1991-1998 (Box R3427)
    - RF 92088 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION - SPECIAL PROGRAMME IN HUMAN REPRODUCTION, 1991-1999 (Box R3427)
- AC.2001.071: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-2001; AC.2001.071; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2001.071.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 92092 #64 - AUSTRALIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY - WEST AFRICAN RESEARCH GROUP ON SEXUAL NETWORKING, 1990-1999 (Box R3428)
    - RF 92094 #28 - MAROPE, MMANTSETSA - MATHEMATICS GENDER GAP AT JUNIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL LEVEL, 1993-2000 (Box R3428)
    - RF 92094 #37 - INTERNATIONAL COLLABORATIVE FOR SCIENCE EDUCATION AND THE ENVIRONMENT, INC. - OPPORTUNITIES FOR GIRLS IN KENYA AND TANZANIA, 1990-1996 (Box R3428)
    - RF 92094 #54 - ZESAGULI, JOSEPHINE - ADIA: ZIMBABWE SCIENCE TEACHER TRAINING PROGRAM, 1991-1998 (Box R3428)
    - RF 92095 #40 - WILDLIFE SOCIETY OF MALAWI - ENVIRONMENTAL EDUCATION PROJECT IN CHIKWAWA, 1994-2000 (Box R3428)
    - RF 93001 #196 - WASHINGTON STATE UNIVERSITY - RICE BLAST FUNGUS, 1989-1997 (Box R3429)
    - RF 93003 #211 - SOUTH CHINA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - RICE GENES LINKAGE, 1990-1997 (Box R3429)
    - RF 93013 #511 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY- RESIDENT FELLOWS: CENTER FOR MEDIA, CULTURE AND HISTORY, 1993-1997 (Box R3429)
    - RF 93013 #512 - UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO - RESIDENT FELLOWS AT CHICAGO HUMANITIES INSTITUTE, 1992-1998 (Box R3429)
    - RF 93013 #513 - HOWARD UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWS AT CENTER FOR STUDY OF CULTURE AND DEVELOPMENT IN AFRICA, 1993-1997 (Box R3429)
    - RF 93013 #521 - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWS AT CENTER FOR CRITICAL ANALYSIS OF CONTEMPORARY CULTURE, 1993-1998 (Box R3429)
    - RF 93013 #523 - EL COLEGIO DE LA FRONTERA NORTE (MEXICO)- HISTORY OF MEXICO-US BORDER REGION, 1991-1996 (Box R3430)
    - RF 93013 #530 - CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - LATIN AMERICAN CULTURAL STUDIES PROGRAMS SURVEY, 1991-1998 (Box R3430)
    - RF 93013 #530 - CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - LATIN AMERICAN CULTURAL STUDIES PROGRAMS SURVEY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-1998 (Box R3430)
    - RF 93018 #10 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL OF MUSEUMS (FRANCE) - EVALUATE TRAINING COURSE; TRANSLATION SERVICES AT ICOM MEETING, 1996-1997 (Box R3430)
    - RF 93018 #11 - WEST AFRICAN MUSEUMS PROGRAM - EXTERNAL EVALUATION, 1996-1997 (Box R3430)
    - RF 93018 #9 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - PARTICIPATION OF AFRICAN ARTISTS AT 1995 AFRICAN STUDIES ASSOCIATION MEETING (Box R3430)
    - RF 93022 #186 - NATIONAL LABORATORY OF PROTEIN ENGINEERING AND PLANT GENETIC ENGINEERING (CHINA) - MOLECULAR MECHANISMS OF SENESCENCE IN G2 PEA, 1993-1997 (Box R3430)
    - RF 93022 #189 - NANJING AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - PHYSIOLOGICAL IMPACT OF ADDING TRANSGENES TO RICE, 1993-1996 (Box R3430)
    - RF 93022 #190 - ACADEMIA SINICA - SHANGHAI INSTITUTE OF BIOCHEMISTRY - MOLECULAR BIOLOGY OF GENES ENCODING AUXINBINDING PROTEINS, 1993-1998 (Box R3430)
    - RF 93022 #192 - UNIVERSITY OF SIERRA LEONE - CHANGES IN CHILDREN'S IMMUNE RESPONSE AFTER TREATMENT WITH INVERMECTIN, 1992-2000 (Box R3430)
    - RF 93022 #194 - CHONJU WOO SUK UNIVERSITY (KOREA)- SALT-STRESS ON CALMODULIN SYSTEM IN PLANTS, 1992-2001 (Box R3430)
- AC.2001.083: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-2000; AC.2001.083; 11.79 Cubic Feet 9 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2001.083.1; 11.79 Cubic Feet 9 record storage boxes
    - RF 93022 #195 - UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL DE LA PLATA (ARGENTINA) - TAXONOMY AND ECOLOGY OF INSECT PARASITIC NEMATODES, 1992-1997 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #196 - UNIVERSITY OF MAIDUGURI (NIGERIA) - "MYCOIDES CLUSTER" STUDY, 1992-1998 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #200 - HOSPITAL INFANTIL DE MEXICO, FEDERICO GOMEZ - PATHOGENESIS OF SALMONELLA TYPHI, 1993-1999 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #201 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF IMMUNOLOGY (INDIA) - ANALYSIS OF PEPTIDE REPERTOIRES OF MHC PROTEINS, 1991-2000 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #203 - UNIVERSIDADE DE SAO PAOLO (BRAZIL) - THICK FILAMENT ASSEMBLY, 1993-2000 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #205 - CENTRE FOR BIOCHEMICAL TECHNOLOGY (INDIA) - ANTHRAX LETHAL TOXIN, 1993-2000 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #206 - SRI VENKATESWARA UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - EFFECT OF FSH AND TESTOSTERONE ON MRNA TRANSCRIPTION AND GENE EXPRESSION IN RAT CELLS, 1993-1999 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #207 - UNIVERSIDAD DE BUENOS AIRES (ARGENTINA) - OXIDATIVE STRESS IN TESTICULAR CELLS CAUSED BY ZINC DEFICIENCY, 1990-1999 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #209 - KOTHARI, SHANKER L., 1990-1997 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #210 - PLANT GENETIC RESOURCES CENTER (ETHIOPIA) - IN VITRO TECHNIQUES FOR GENETIC MATERIAL COLLECTION, EVALUATION, PRESERVATION, AND IMPROVEMENT, 1992-1997 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #211 - PANJAB UNIVERSITY (INDIA)- CONSTRUCTION OF RECOMBINANT VACCINE STRAIN OF SALMONELLA, 1993-2000 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #212 - UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL AUTONOMA DE MEXICO - EFFECT OF ADENINE NUCLEOTIDES, 1993-1998 (Box R3431)
    - RF 93022 #213 - TRAUB-CSEKO, YARA MARIA, 1990-2000 (Box R3432)